import {Difficulty} from "../constants/difficulty-enum";

export const MULTIPLE_CHOICE_QUESTIONS: MultipleChoiceQuestion[] = [
    {
        index: 1,
        questionText: 'The first question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 2,
        questionText: 'The second question - answer is 1',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 3,
        questionText: 'The third question - answer is 2',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 4,
        questionText: 'The forth question - answer is 3',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 5,
        questionText: 'The fith question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 6,
        questionText: 'The sixth question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 7,
        questionText: 'The seventh question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 8,
        questionText: 'The eight question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 9,
        questionText: 'The nineth question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 10,
        questionText: 'The tenth question - answer is 2',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 11,
        questionText: 'The twelveth question - answer is 1',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 12,
        questionText: 'The thirteenth question - answer is 3',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 13,
        questionText: 'The forteenth question - answer is 0',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 14,
        questionText: 'The fithteenth question - answer is 2',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
    {
        index: 15,
        questionText: 'The sixteenth question - answer is 1',
        answers: ['Answer 1', 'Answer 2', 'Answer 3', 'Answer 4'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        difficulty: Difficulty.MEDIUM
    },
]

export const MULTIPLE_CHOICE_QUESTIONS_LENGTH = MULTIPLE_CHOICE_QUESTIONS.length